[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What distinctive anatomical characteristic do the scorpions from the Hemiscorpiidae family possess, which makes them easily recognizable?", "correct_answer": "Their body is flat and broad.", "incorrect_answers": ["They have only four legs.", "Their sting is intense red", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which shark is the fastest swimmer?", "correct_answer": "mako shark", "incorrect_answers": ["goblin shark", "nurse shark", "sandtiger shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is used for the behavior exhibited by male giraffes that are engaged in a fight?", "correct_answer": "Necking", "incorrect_answers": ["Hoofing", "Tailing", "Horning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which year is most significant to Napoleon Bonaparte?", "correct_answer": "1800 AD", "incorrect_answers": ["1700 AD", "1600 AD", "2525 AD"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Peter Rabbit, the first patented soft toy, initially appeared in a childrens story written by this author.", "correct_answer": "Beatrix Potter", "incorrect_answers": ["Lewis Carroll", "Paulette Bourgeois", "Dr. Seuss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What way of defence do wombats use when they feel threatened?", "correct_answer": "Kicking", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Running", "Climbing on trees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average lifespan of a lion in the wild?", "correct_answer": "10-14 years", "incorrect_answers": ["6-9 years", "20-24 years", "15-20 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who created the collectible card game Magic: The Gathering?", "correct_answer": "Richard Garfield", "incorrect_answers": ["Bennie Smith", "Gary Gygax", "Mike Flores"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first recorded use of the word purple in the English language dates back to what year?", "correct_answer": "AD 975", "incorrect_answers": ["AD 1400", "AD 251", "AD 1023"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1924 who was the German mathematician who developed a proof showing that blood types were genetic?", "correct_answer": "Felix Bernstein", "incorrect_answers": ["Franklin McLean", "Charles  R. Drew", "William Osler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Yellow River is the second largest river after the Yangtze in what country?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "Japan", "South Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This bear, also known as a Silvertip bear, is native to North America.", "correct_answer": "Grizzly Bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Panda Bear", "Polar Bear", "Red Panda Bear"]}]